It's my life.
It's your life.
Fighting for tomorrow.
Go catch what you really want.
I want more. Any one more.
Come on, open up the door.
It's my life. It's your life.
Run like a winter fire.
I know you're strong.
Believe you can achieve your goal.
Let's keep on going.
I'll not stay.
Let's do it again, you
know what I mean, baby.
No one can make my dream come true?
Don't you feel it?
I really don't know what is
Something is testing me every day.
Hey, let's go.
Let's fly away.
I know I never wanna come back here.
Hey, let's go.
Let's fly away. The great
end of the unknown rules.
Standing up, blowing up.
My dream is getting wilder.
I'm not afraid, beat me, hit me.
I will never turn around.
Another day, another chance.
You know it's never too late.
If I can do it, so can you.
Only we are.
It's my life, it's your life.
But if you don't want to
get what you really want.
I want more, anyone more.
Come on, open up the door.
It's my life. It's your life.
Run like a wind, jump high, yeah, yeah.
I know you're strong.
Believe you cannot achieve your goal.
Let's keep on going, roaring.
It's my life, it's your life.
Fighting for your eyes that
I want, but your weary ones.
I want more, and you want more.
Come on, open up the gate.
It's my life, it's your life.
Shine like a star to be good, yeah.
I know you're strong.
Just that you can't achieve your best.
Let's keep on going. Out of day.
You make my day every day.
Don't let your guard down.
Doflamingo is quite formidable.
I wonder, Sengoku.
Where did you find this intel?
Who do you work with?
Vice Admiral Saru.
We got a call from the
lookout ship on Minion Island.
Beryl's hideout is on fire?
Yes.
We're going to investigate it now.
Call them back.
If the pirates find out we sent
battleships, then the deal is off.
Check the coastal area instead.
Report to me if you see anyone suspicious.
Yes, ma ’am.
Captain Baratie.
We can worry about our injuries later.
This is a five-billion berry deal.
We have to get that fruit back right now!
Karoo.
Good.
You made it back after all. Silence.
Look, Law!
I brought a surprise with me!
I heard gunshots and saw
the building burning.
so i thought something
might have happened to you
hey can i get a smile
and a thank you we did it
pal i'm gonna save your
life you should be happy
yeah but even if i eat that devil
fruit i i might not get better right
you'll get better so open wide law eat
up and heal up what are you waiting for
it's gross i don't care just eat
the damn thing you chew and swallow
No fair. Karoo.
I wasn't ready.
Now I have weird powers.
I didn't even ask for this, you know.
Hey. Karoo?
It's fine, okay?
I did my part.
And now you can go cure yourself.
We just outsmarted Doflamingo.
Why in the snow? He'll get sick.
Are you worn out or what?
Let me turn you over!
You're covered in blood! What happened?
Did someone shoot you?
I got clumsy. Damn it!
Why did you say something sooner?
Wait a sec.
You better! Come on!
Get better!
Stop pleading!
Don't be sorry.
Like I said, you need knowledge to
make the Op-Op powers work. Help me!
Tell me what to do!
You got shot because of me!
I have to fix this!
Law, don't worry about me.
I won't die from something like this.
Kara!
But we still need to staunch the
bleeding, or I'll be in bad shape.
Listen carefully, okay?
We got the op-op through
just like I said we would.
But it's gonna take more than
that to stop Duffy in his tracks.
This isn't over just yet.
I know you're in bad shape,
but I need to ask a favor.
There's a Navy lookout ship on
the west coast of this island.
Take this and hand this over to them.
It's not a trick; if a marine sees this,
they would know exactly what to do with it.
This one little package will save a country,
a faraway kingdom called Dress Rosa.
I don't get it.
Besides, I told you before
how much I hate the navy.
Your father was a great doctor.
Right as soon as you deliver
this, we'll get off this island.
And then, we can travel the
world together, just you and I.
Marines.
Okay, he's alone.
Take this, hmm, a secret message.
I don't know who gave this
to you, but I'm grateful.
I'll take good care of
this, so don't you worry.
But you sound kind of
sick—kid—are you okay?
I can trust you.
Can I, uh—huh—like I said, I'll make sure.
said I'll make sure that
letter gets to the right hand.
No, listen, I need you to help someone.
He was shot.
He's in really bad shape.
Please, you have to save him.
I don't know what I would do if he died.
He got hurt because of me.
I found someone to give you first aid!
Hang in there!
Vergo, Corazon, what
are you doing out here?
Did you just talk? Oh, crap.
So that was his secret mission, huh?
You know each other?
Wait, did you call him?
Who's there? Go.
an extremely powerful
individual right now—he's
away from the family
on a secret operation,
but the details of that
are between him and Dofi.
That guy has nothing to do
with you, so forget about him.
Don't
you dare that!
He
was infiltrating the Navy all this time.
I see.
What a sick joke!
There are probably
thousands of marines here.
And somehow this bastard gets the letter.
I
get the message loud and clear.
Give
it back!
Cora—
You
listen to me.
He's heard enough.
Give
it away, you bastard.
You
work for Doflamingo, and
how would you know that?
I get it—you must be that new
boy, Law from the White Town.
Dofi told
me all about you, about how
you two ran off—traitors.
You need to learn some respect.
Kid—if you know my position, then you
should have the sense to call me Mr.
Vergo.
You really spilled the
beans in this secret report of yours.
The Navy got a hold of info like this
and that would be the end of the family,
but we have so much unfinished business.
You will betray the
family over one child.
You're nothing but a
rat.
nothing but a rat
A disgrace. That's the second Corazon.
You think I didn't suspect you?
I remember when you were
eight and went missing,
only to show up again 14 years later.
If it was up to me, I would have
turned you away on the spot.
But Duffy trusted you, because
you're his brother after all.
You earned this fate.
Come on!
Nora!
He's gonna die!
Whoa, hold on.
You didn't kill them, did you?
All right.
So what did you find out?
Corazon was a spy for the Navy.
He's been working with them on
a plot to take out the family.
Careful.
They're probably on to
our Devil Fruit plan.
Where are you right now?
I was watching the rendezvous
spot on Swallow Island earlier,
but I noticed two warships
approach from a distance.
After that, I couldn't hide
from the truth anymore.
My sweet little brother was
bearing his fangs at me.
Although that's unfortunate, it did
remind me of something important.
You guys are my real family.
I suppose I had to face
reality sooner or later.
At any rate, we're at
Minion Island right now.
Close to you, I think.
Pity we didn't arrive here a bit sooner.
The first thing we saw when
we got here was a bunch of
Beryl's pirates screaming about
the Devil Fruit being stolen.
Corazon's work. I'm sure.
In other words, don't let him go anywhere.
He has the abob fruit.
Okay, I'll make sure...
Damn it!
Oh, ran away already.
Well, no worries.
I'm sure they're still
on the island, after all.
We'll hunt them down soon enough.
Hey, uh, you seen this?
No, no, no.
What now?
That's creepy.
Those things are sharp as a knife
and rock solid too, damn it!
Someone trapped us in here.
What are those?
One of Dofi's abilities?
I would imagine; I've
never seen it myself.
But one thing is perfectly
clear: there's nowhere to run!
He's using the parasite string, of course.
We're locked in a cage.
This is a living hell.
Cora, what's going on? Help me.
I don't think I can save myself,
but maybe I can still save him.
This may be the end of the road, but I
hope you'll remember me when I'm gone.
And promise I'll go out with a smile.
Maybe it's not worth much, but if
you do think back on me someday?
I'd rather you remember me smiling.
We gotta get moving, buddy.
Let's go.
Duffy, this is our boss. So this one
little guy knocked everyone out cold, huh?
You must have some powerful Haki
Brother, you can't do this!
Stop living!
Stop living! Why?
Why did you take my power from me?
Do you want me to give you
the strength to take revenge?
Father, we have to live with
this mess you put us in!
Unless I take your head back
to the Holy Land, that is!
Do Flamingo, Rosinante,
you have a very foolish father.
I'm sorry.
It's madness. I don't
know how to describe this.
Suddenly, the whole town was
surrounded by some kind of giant cage.
We can't get in and all.
The pirates went insane;
they're screaming and running!
and cutting each other down.
It's a massacre.
3A, don't run away.
You got to help me.
There has to be some way out of here.
Don't go.
We need you.
It's the dog you're holding for the money.
3A, damn, where the hell
did that brat run off to?
It's life or death and he's gone.
Guess our strongest fighter
is our biggest coward, huh?
We'll have to make...
Doflamingo!
So you're the bastard who ran
off with our op-op fruit, huh?
Who ran off?
I'm here, you drunk.
If you hadn't lost it, I'd be
taking that fruit right now. Oh!
Let's start hauling these away.
Sounds good.
Just make sure you grab
every last big cake.
This is exciting!
Not too shabby.
They're pretty loaded
for a bunch of chumps.
We still need to find Corazon, remember?
So stop fooling around.
Buffalo!
Have you spotted anything yet?
Everything's burned to a crisp!
If there's any survivors,
I sure don't see them!
I caught a message.
Search for any possible victims.
We took a boy into protective
custody at the coast.
The Navy said they took
a boy into custody!
It's you! Dorry!
It sounds like Gladius ran into Corazon!
Listen, Lar.
Stay still and they won't find you.
This is a trick that always
works against pirates.
I saw Corazon go that way.
Lao-G, over here.
Why can't I open this lid?
Is something sitting on it?
Ah, yeah!
That's Mertz.
Why have you been pretending that
you can't talk all this time?
Because I've got nothing to talk about.
Not to garbage like you punks.
Insolence!
You made a fool of the young master.
You've done enough, Gladius.
We can't have him die before
the young master arrives.
Let us have some fun.
You were trying to lure the
Navy into an Alto war with us,
weren't you, you lying bastard?
You're quite the little villain, huh?
Hey, the Young Master's here.
I haven't seen you in
six months, Korra's Zone.
You have nowhere to go?
Well, you're safe with us.
Marine Code 0-1-7-4-6.
Rocinante.
Commander from HQ.
Captain of the Don Quixote family.
Doflamingo.
I've been working undercover to
prevent a tragedy of your making.
That has been my mission.
I took a submarine.
I lied to you. Sorry.
I didn't want you to hate me, that's all.
Why are you saying this now? I
already knew, of course I did.
an apology you really
think we'll show mercy on
you now i don't have the
patience for your insipid
little jokes so you'd
better answer my questions
now where's the op-op
fruit and where is law
That's long gone. Law ate it
right up. In other words, he's a
power holder that's how he was
able to get out of your cage
there's a navy lookout ship
nearby that probably took him
into protective custody already
which means he's safe from you
why didn't you tell me
sooner this is urgent
I swear I got here as fast
as I can. We're sorry!
A boy?
Lucky coincidence, I guess.
Since Law is here.
I'll undo the birdcage.
Go check into that, quickly!
It seems that fate is conspiring
to keep you alive, Law.
One guardian angel after another
keeps swooping in to save you.
All of you, prepare to set sail!
If what we just heard was true,
we need to attack that Navy ship.
Then we'll take back Law.
Don't bother.
What would you do with him?
What would I do?
Isn't it obvious?
If Law ate the Abob fruit like you
said, he needs to be educated properly.
So, the boy can die for me.
You really have gone out of your way
to cause me trouble, haven't you?
Why do you insist on undermining your
brother? Why are you forcing me to do this?
kill my own flesh and blood yet again you
point that gun but I know you can't shoot
me because in the end you're just like
your father when a pirate sees a treasure
chest like that one it
can't resist picking
it up and taking it on
their ship with them
that means as long as you stay in here
you'll definitely have a chance to get out
of this cage so don't move what about you
that's okay you ate the fruit that's the
only thing dopey's really interested in
besides he and i are brothers remember he
might get mad sure but it's not like he's
gonna kill his own
flesh and blood and calm
now even if you rumble around
in there it won't make any noise
i'll see you in the next town
all right hey law i love you kid
this is not what you promised me at all
Karoo you said he wasn't gonna kill you
Law wouldn't obey you
anyway, Duffy. Sorry.
He only had three years to live, and he
knew that, but he kept fighting anyway.
He grew much stronger.
He found himself again.
He's not the same lost child who threw
himself before a killer like you.
He has nothing to gain from someone
who only longs for destruction.
He's above that, so you leave him the
hell alone cuz laws finally free now
You say that again, who
did you call the monster?
He's on fire!
See?
Slept well, right?
Putting out!
Not yet.
I have to survive just
a little bit longer.
Pull the ship over here.
Because if I die now, the spell I
cast will be broken in an instant.
And if you cry or make a single noise.
Anyone on the island might hear it.
Pick yourself up, law.
Go silently.
Unseen.
Farther.
And farther.
There's nothing to bite you down anymore.
Not the iron borders of Whitetown
Or the sickness that haunted you.
Your life is finally your own.
Hurry it up.
That's Zuru's warship damn it
So don't be sad you're free now
Oh, my God!